{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117840609","data":{"timestamp":" 947117840609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117844962","data":{"timestamp":" 947117844962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117851541","data":{"timestamp":" 947117851541"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117857706","data":{"timestamp":" 947117857706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" di"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117864788","data":{"timestamp":" 947117864788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117878754","data":{"timestamp":" 947117878754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" du"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117884980","data":{"timestamp":" 947117884979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117892882","data":{"timestamp":" 947117892882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117899934","data":{"timestamp":" 947117899934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" no"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117911078","data":{"timestamp":" 947117911078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117918727","data":{"timestamp":" 947117918727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117927883","data":{"timestamp":" 947117927883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117934265","data":{"timestamp":" 947117934265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" pe"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117944176","data":{"timestamp":" 947117944176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947117949969","data":{"timestamp":" 947117949966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_031705"," gameId":" d2d13929-dc14-4bad-9cea-960e855586b3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}